I'm sorry, sir.
I can't take this job.
Why? Not enough money?
No, I just can't handle it.
No matter how much you offer,
I just can't.
Are you afraid of Nam Gi Joon?
Yes.
I was there and saw it all.
Eleven years ago.
And do you believe it?
About Nam Gi Suk.
do you really think
that he was killed by minors?
Do you think this is even possible?
- Congratulations, pastor.
- Good evening.
- Congratulations.
- Let's go inside.
Terrible weather, huh?
Where is Jun Mo now?
He is with Kim Chung Seok.
Tell him to hide Jun Mo in Yangpyeong.
No, you'd better do it yourself.
Let our boys be policemen.
What police officers?
i want to know
who first found Nam Gi Suk
who investigates the case
and did the little gangs really do it.
Let's find out all the details.
I listen.
WITHOUT MERCY
DE'CRO HOTEL
Mr. Gu.
We must go immediately.
The chairman ordered
take you to a secret place in Yangpyeong.
It is necessary to leave already.
And I have to go, where will my father say?
sir
Nam Gi Joon is looking for you.
That is,
you all make yourself so much trouble
because of one scumbag, right?
sir i think you don't understand
how serious is Nam Gi Joon…
That Nam Gi Joon gave up on you!
Why are you all so afraid of him?
Ahoy!
What the hell?
Everyone is gone.
What is the matter with him?
And why did you come?
Sir, we have to go. I will take you
what are you doing
I'm taking you to Yangpyeong.
How much longer to clean up after him?
So
You can't come here.
“Take Jun Mo to Yangpyeong.
Beat if necessary." This is the order of the chairman.
Are you out of your mind?
i do it
because you don't know how to work properly.
Damn scum!
Is Gu Jun Mo upstairs?
Let me go, bitch!
Let him go!
are you crazy
Do, as he says, a goat.
Devil.
Sir, we must leave immediately.
You must leave immediately.
Let it go already.
Devil. please
listen to me at least once?
- Well, I want to see.
- No, really...
That scum is here at all.
Please let's go. Listen to me!
Bastard!
Gee Jun! stop, okay?
Will you stop at my request?
Please stop!
And you walk well.
Sir, are you all right?
Get up. Well, get up!
Take it away.
get up Immediately!
I have to go. Let's sew from here!
Devil.
How many times have I said just obey?
Who the hell is this? Devil.
Jeon Hye Bum, that fucking goat.
Gu Jun Mo!
- Ah!
- Do not touch the door.
- Stop!
- Away!
Devil! Throw away!
You fucking idiot!
Is Jun Mo okay?
Yes, sir. A little scared,
but everything is fine with him.
I'm taking him to Yangpyeong.
Increase security.
So that no one knows that he is there. Clear?
Don't worry.
Will this damn ride ever end?
sir
We have arrived.
Should it be cut too?
I don't know, bitch!
Think for yourself!
But no, we will be caught
and will be beaten to death again.
We can't just run away.
Are you our strategist now, bastard?
I said to go immediately
and you 40 minutes
sat on the sralnik, bastard.
Gotta run while we still can, idiot.
- You know...
- Mr. Sim.
Bonsan is currently busy with Nam Gi Joon,
so if we want to escape
this is our only chance.
I'll bring you some coffee.
What, are you going somewhere?
No, I wasn't going anywhere.
I just got back.
I traveled on business.
I'm exhausted.
You know where Gu Jun Mo is, right?
Well, because
I already said.
I just came back from a business trip.
He must be hiding.
Even "Cemetery" will not find him.
find him
I give one day.
And yet, Mr. Choi?
do you really think
that you won't win anything, only lose?
Prosecutor Lee.
What is the reason?
What are you talking about?
Listening.
Why was it draining me?
Mr. Choi.
I am a prosecutor
and my father is a gang boss, so I know.
Prosecutors and gangsters are not so different.
Those and those put
interests of the group over personal.
So what do you think, Mr. Choi?
You think, do not pay attention to death
is Mr. Nam really the best for the company?
I support the chairman's decision.
No, I understand father's reasoning.
Gu Jun Mo's death will start a war.
Of course he was scared.
All that he built
can fall apart in an instant.
But I see it as an opportunity.
A chance to end the Bonsan Corporation.
A chance for the company "Chuvun"
take everything
Honey, you couldn't
take out garbage for recycling,
just this week?
I won't be able to come home.
- Couldn't you...
- Mr. Kim!
Wait.
Honey, I have to go. Rebound.
Mr. Kim Chun Suk!
Did they call?
Let's continue there,
where we stayed yesterday.
What are you talking about?
About Nam Gi Joon.
Tell me about him.
About Gi Joon?
That is, you are finally interested...
Nam Gi Joon.
Mr. Gu.
What do you know about Nam Gi Joon?
Once upon a time
Nam Gi Joon was a god to us.
Because he did it to Chuvun Corporation
and Bonsan, what they are today.
Boss! There's the Bonsan gang...
When Lee Choo Woon and Goo Bong San
worked for the head O,
they collided
with Busan's biggest gang.
Mr. Oh wanted to go to Japan,
therefore sought control over the port of Pusan.
He was going to send the two of them
take Pusan, but they were too late.
Busan's gang attacked first.
They held on,
as much as they could, but they were overcome.
They are almost finished.
Kill them!
And then Nam Gi Joon appeared.
Kill him!
Die!
Damn abomination!
What the hell?
We understood again,
that Nam Gi Joon didn't care,
who he was against or how many there are.
From that moment Lee Choo Woon and Goo Bong San
significantly strengthened their power.
Agov, Son of Vone.
According to rumors, the head O
wanted to transfer the business to them, not to his son.
What is it, son? Do you want to say something?
No, not really.
Thank you.
These rumors were a problem.
Mr. O's son did not like it.
Are you sure that this is the order of the chief's son?
Yes.
I thought my only way to survive was
is to tell you the truth
and beg me to forgive.
Please believe. I beg
Here.
Listen to this one.
Listen. Please here.
Here, listen.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Lee Choo Woon and Goo Bong San! Kill them.
Chief O's son crossed the border.
It turns out that he ordered to kill them both.
Then all hell broke loose.
- Hell.
- Shutdown?
Go turn on the electricity.
And who are you?
Lee Choo Woon and Goo Bong Sang.
Bring them to me.
What's going on?
I thought that I should kill the son of the leader -
the best step for the company.
What kind of jokes are these?
- Fool!
- Boss, you have to make a choice.
Or we'll let Mr. O kill us,
or we will kill him.
Gi Jun.
Sir,
it's all Chu Woon.
I didn't know anything about it.
I swear
Thank you for protecting your head,
while I was gone
I was hoping…
that you didn't do it.
sorry
Gi Jun.
Why did you do that?
I just don't understand.
Why did you come this far?
The son of the leader...
Say you didn't kill him.
Does it matter?
Sorry.
I was late.
One day.
In just one day, the leader of O died.
And then...
Lee Choo Woon and Goo Bong San
captured everything.
After that incident
a rule appeared to keep the peace.
"All those who cause trouble,
must pay for it."
And Nam Gi Joon stood
the first victim of this rule.
He helped them take everything
but he started the whole mess.
He had merit…
So they only cut the Achilles tendon?
Yes.
Maybe they were afraid of him -
and Lee Choo Woon
and Mr. Gu.
So…
You expect me to believe
I will sit here in this nonsense.
Yes?
OK.
You can be afraid of him all your life.
sorry
I had to do everything
to stop Gu Jun Mo.
Everything is fine. Don't worry.
Did President Gu's son kill Gi Seok?
Gi Jun, you need to think again.
i understand how you feel
and we can't
confront the Bonsan gang by yourself.
You don't need to help me.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm afraid for you.
listen
I will talk to Lee Choo Woon…
He won't do anything.
What?
He knows it's Gu Jun Mo,
but ordered to forget about it.
It's just proof
how little Gi Seok meant to him.
Devil.
let me out
Freaks
Let me out!
Ahoy!
This is not a home, this is a prison! Freaks!
Let me out!
Let me out of here! Badge!
Yes, I am going to Seoul.
- Call in case of anything.
- Yes, sir.
GU JUNG MO
how are you bro
Hey, I have a job for you.
Velychenka.
And to be damn clear,
this time
this is an order.
You have to do everything properly.
An order?
Today. Call back about the place.
How many are there?
Only one.
One?
GU JUNG MO
DIRECTOR
Mr. Gu.
So you say,
that the whole problem is
that Nam Gi Joon is still alive.
So as soon as he dies…
there will be no more problems.
Sorry?
Nam Gi Joon.
I will take care of him.
I rewatched Nam Gi Suk's case,
but something is wrong.
FOUND THE BODY
AND REPORTED BY HAN SOK YOUN
"Found the body
Han Seok Yoon."
Investigating Officer - Han Seok Yoon,
but he also found the body.
Find it.
Bring it to me.
And immediately.
Yes, sir.
friend
You didn't get hurt yesterday, did you?
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
How are you, are you okay?
Listen, it looks like
Gu will not back down.
It doesn't matter how good you are, okay?
You are not against him, but against all of Bonsan.
If you don't back down, it's very dangerous.
To all of Bonsan - is that including you?
Well, stop it.
I remember how in the past
when we did everything together...
showdowns on the square were the crowning moment.
At least then
people were responsible for their actions.
Why did you want to meet?
Here, take it.
Gu Jun Mo is hiding there.
So what?
I won't be able to run away forever.
Don't worry about me.
I was going to leave the company anyway.
Aww, Gi Joon.
go
and finish what you have to, okay?
REPAIR
FLOORS 10-13 CLOSED
Forgive me, my friend.
Meet Nam Gi Joon.
He then asks where I am.
When he asks,
act as if he tortured you,
and lead him into my trap.
Your daughter just started walking, right?
Want to see her grow up?
Well, Mr. Kim!
Is Nam Gi Joon more important than family?
If you want to save the life of the family,
he must be killed.
OKUR
Did you do the job?
say
Is that scumbag dead?
hold on
I will come for you.
WITHOUT MERCY
11 YEARS AGO
Son of the leader...
Say you didn't kill him.
Does it matter?
Translation of subtitles: Olga Tsiatska